http://www.cidrap.umn.edu/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
University of Minnesota. Driven to Discover.
Privacy Policy
Online Privacy StatementThe policy of the University of Minnesota and of the Center for Infectious Disease Research and Policy (CIDRAP) is to respect the privacy of all Web site visitors to the extent permitted by law. This online privacy statement is intended to inform you of the ways in which CIDRAP Web sites collect information, the uses to which that information will be put, and the ways in which we will protect any information you choose to provide us.CIDRAP Web sites use Google Analytics for gathering statistics about Web traffic. Use of cookies by Google Analytics is covered by their privacy policy. CIDRAP Web pages can be identified by page URLs that begin with the following:CIDRAP Web sitePage URLInfectious Disease Information and other related topics              http://www.cidrap.umn.edu/There are five types of information that a site may collect during your visit: network traffic logs, Web visit logs, cookies, learning tracking information, and information voluntarily provided by you.Network Traffic LogsIn the course of ensuring network security and consistent service for all users, the University employs software programs to do such things as monitor network traffic, identify unauthorized access or access to nonpublic information, detect computer viruses and other software that might damage University computers or the network, and monitor and tune the performance of the University network. In the course of such monitoring, these programs may detect such information as e-mail headers, addresses from network packets, and other information. Information from these activities is used only for the purpose of maintaining the security and performance of the University's networks and computer systems. Personally identifiable information from these activities is not released to external parties without your consent unless required by law.Web Visit LogsUniversity Web sites routinely collect and store information from online visitors to help manage those sites and improve service. This information includes the pages visited on the site, the date and time of the visit, the internet address (URL or IP address) of the referring site, the domain name and IP address from which the access occurred, the version of browser used, the capabilities of the browser, and search terms used on our search engines. University sites make no attempt to identify individual visitors from this information: any personally identifiable information is not released to external parties without your consent unless required by law.CookiesCookies are pieces of information stored by your Web browser on behalf of a Web site and returned to the Web site on request. A University site may use cookies for two purposes: to carry data about your current session at the site from one Web page to the next, and to identify you to the site between visits. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you may turn them off in your browser, or may set your browser to ask you before accepting a new cookie. Some pages may not function properly if the cookies are turned off. Unless otherwise notified on this site, we will not store data, other than for these two purposes, in cookies. Cookies remain on your computer, and accordingly we neither store cookies on our computers nor forward them to any external parties. Unless otherwise notified on this site, we do not use cookies to track your movement among different Web sites and do not exchange cookies with other entities.Information Voluntarily Provided by YouIn the course of using this Web site, you may choose to provide us with information to help us serve your needs. For example, you may send us electronic mail to request information or you may sign up for a mailing list. Any personally identifiable information you send us will be used only for the purpose indicated. Requests for information will be directed to the appropriate staff to respond to the request, and may be recorded to help us update our site to better respond to similar requests. We will not sell, exchange or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information without your consent, except to the extent required by law. We do not retain the information longer than necessary for normal operations. Each Web page requesting information discloses the purpose of that information. If you do not wish to have the information used in that manner, you are not required to provide it. Please contact the person listed on the specific page, or listed below, with questions or concerns on the use of personally identifiable information.The Influenza Training Modules Portal (http://www.cidrap.umn.edu/ongoing-programs/influenza-training) gathers several pieces of information about you.  This information includes data entered by you during registration to the portal or to the Avian Flu School section, and after completing a module (the “post-test” survey).  This information is summarized without identifiers and is reported back to our funding sources. Your progress through a module is recorded as is your test score at the end of the module.CIDRAP sites provide links to other World Wide Web sites and resources. We do not control these sites and resources and are not responsible for their availability, content, or delivery of services. In particular, external sites are not bound by the CIDRAP online privacy policy; they may have their own policies or none at all. You can tell you are leaving a CIDRAP Web site by noting the URL of the destination site.If you have questions about general University of Minnesota security measures see the University policy, Collecting Information From Visitors To University Web Sites.If you have questions about CIDRAP sites, the collection of information, or its online privacy statement, contact the site administrator at cidrap@umn.edu.
Newsletter Sign-up
Get CIDRAP news and other free newsletters.Sign up now»
OUR UNDERWRITERS
Unrestricted financial support provided by Become an underwriter»
Main menu
Home
News & Perspective
Infectious Disease Topics
Antimicrobial Stewardship
Ongoing ProgramsAntimicrobial Stewardship
CEIRS Pandemic Planning
Chronic Wasting Disease
Newsletter Signup
CIDRAP - Center for Infectious Disease Research and PolicyOffice of the Vice President for Research, University of Minnesota, Minneapolis, MN© 2020 Regents of the University of Minnesota. All rights reserved.The University of Minnesota is an equal opportunity educator and employer.CIDRAP  |  Office of the Vice President for Research  |  Contact U of M  |  Privacy Policy
